<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel><title>My Awesome Blog</title><link>http://bbhood.ca/blog/index.html</link>
<description>A blog about whatever I feel like</description><language>en</language>
<lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:06:20 -0230</lastBuildDate>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:06:20 -0230</pubDate>
<atom:link href="http://bbhood.ca/blog/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
<item><title>
Test of the blog-- Maybe I should learn vim?
</title><description><![CDATA[

<p>This post is being written using <b>NANO</b>. I should probably learn to use <b>VIM</b>, as it does seem like it can do a lot more, much quicker, but I worry that getting used to VIM will make me age a billion years in a second, telling my partners that I can't use Netflix because they use too much DRM for my tastes. But who knows-- Maybe there's some magic resource out there that makes vim super easy to use over Nano or gives me better appreciation for its feaatures.</p>

<p>Until then, I think I'm going to stick with Nano. As part of my college classes, I'm figuring out Apache servers tomorrow and a bunch of other Linux server related topics, and my eventual goal when it comes to home server use is to have my own image filehost that I use, as I've been burned before by one going down permanently, and the one I'm currently using worries me as to what I can or can't upload and is a bit of a pain. </p>

<p>I'm wondering how this formatting looks, since all of this is being written in Nano and I can't preview it without being annoyed.</p>
<p>Tags: <a href='tag_linux.html'>linux</a>, <a href='tag_nano.html'>nano</a>, <a href='tag_may-2025.html'>may-2025</a></p>
<!-- text end -->
<p id='twitter'><a href='http://twitter.com/intent/tweet?url=http://bbhood.ca/blog/test-of-the-blog---maybe-i-should-learn-vim.html&text=&lt;Type your comment here but please leave the URL so that other people can follow the comments&gt;&via=dokidokigalaxy'>Comments? Tweet</a> 
<a href='https://twitter.com/search?q=http://bbhood.ca/blog/test-of-the-blog---maybe-i-should-learn-vim.html'><span id='count-15543'></span></a>&nbsp;</p>
]]></description><link>http://bbhood.ca/blog/test-of-the-blog---maybe-i-should-learn-vim.html</link>
<guid>http://bbhood.ca/blog/./test-of-the-blog---maybe-i-should-learn-vim.html</guid>
<dc:creator>Maggie</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:06:18 -0230</pubDate></item>
</channel></rss>
